plasticjungle.com 2014-05-24

# Buy and Sell Gift Cards

## Plastic Jungle Privacy Policy

Last Updated December 13, 2012

This Privacy Policy describes the types of personal and non-personal information we collect through the Plastic Jungle Service, how we use such information and to whom and under what circumstances we may disclose it. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and made a part of, the Plastic Jungle Terms of Use, and capitalized terms used and not defined in this policy have the meaning given to them in the Terms. By using the Plastic Jungle Service, you agree to the collection, use and disclosure of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Plastic Jungle Service. 

Plastic Jungle has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, http://www.plasticjungle.com. 

TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy Trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at customersuccess@plasticjungle.com. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here.](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint)

#### Information Collection

##### Information You Provide To Us

We collect personal information from you when you affirmatively provide it to us, such as when you register, post, or contact us. This information may include your name, address, email address, telephone number, mobile phone number, date of birth, Plastic Jungle Service login name and password. In addition, if you choose to buy gift cards through the Plastic Jungle Service, we will ask you for your credit card information or other payment information. We may combine the information you provide us with information we receive about you from other online and offline sources.

##### Information We Collect Automatically

When you use the Plastic Jungle Service, we collect certain information from you, including but not limited to your browser type, operating system, IP address, device ID, Internet service provider, search query you used to find Plastic Jungle through a search engine, and the web site access immediately before and after the Plastic Jungle Service. In addition, we may collect information about your browsing behavior, such as the date and time you access the Plastic Jungle Service, the areas or features of the Plastic Jungle Service you access, the amount of time you spend using the Plastic Jungle Service, the number of times you return to the Plastic Jungle Service and other clickstream information. We may combine this information with the personal information you provide to us.

We (or service providers working on our behalf) may use cookies and web beacons (also called "pixel tags" or "clear gifs") to collect the non-personal information described above. A cookie is a small text file that may be stored on the hard drive of your computer when you access the Plastic Jungle Service. A web beacon is a tiny graphic image that we place on the Plastic Jungle Service, in our emails and in the advertisements we place on other websites. We or our service providers may also use cookies and web beacons: (1) to recognize you when you return to the Plastic Jungle Service; (2) to provide you with customized content, advertising and marketing offers; (3) to measure the effectiveness of the Plastic Jungle Service, our emails and our advertising (for example, by telling us when you open or act upon an email or when you click on one of our advertisements); (4) to monitor Plastic Jungle Service usage; (5) to recognize the affiliate of ours that referred you to the Plastic Jungle Service (if any); (6) to conduct research to improve our content and services; and (7) for other internal business purposes. You are free to decline or delete cookies, but by doing so, you may not be able to use certain features on the Plastic Jungle Service or take full advantage of all of our offerings. Check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. Blocking certain cookies will also block the use of certain web beacons.

We may also use third-party advertising service providers, who may use cookies and web beacons to track your behavior on the Plastic Jungle Service. These service providers may use this information, together with anonymous information about you that they receive from us, to deliver targeted advertisements to you when you are on this Plastic Jungle Service or one or more of the other websites where they deliver targeted advertisements. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [Here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

##### Flash LSOs

We use local shared objects, also known as Flash cookies, to store your preferences such as volume control or high game score, or display content based upon what you view on our site to personalize your visit. Third Parties, with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity, use Flash cookies to collect and store information. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies [click here.](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118)

##### Information Collected Through Our Referral Service

If you choose to use our refer-a-friend mechanism, we will collect your friend's name and email address, which we will use solely for the purpose of sending that person an email. Your friend may contact us at customersuccess@plasticjungle.com to request that we remove his or her information from our database.

##### Information Collected by Third Parties

We may collect information from you when you use our services on another company's website or on a co-branded website. This may include, for example, our Online Gift Card Registry service available on other companies' websites. All information that we collect through such services is subject to this Privacy Policy. All of the information collected is owned and controlled by Plastic Jungle. We may share some of your transactional information and your name and email address in order for our partner to fulfill all or part of your order. Please note that the information you submit on such a website may alternatively be subject to the privacy policy applicable to that site.

##### Accessing Your Personal Information

You may change, update or delete the personal information we have collected from you by going to the My Account page and clicking the "Edit Account Info" button [or by emailing us at [customersuccess@plasticjungle.com](mailto:customersuccess@plasticjungle.com)]. Choosing to withhold or remove certain information may interfere with your ability to utilize the Plastic Jungle Service to its fullest potential. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. While changes you make will be reflected in active user databases promptly, we reserve the right to retain any information you provide for a variety of reasons, to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, including fraud and abuse prevention, archival backups, and data analytics.

#### Information Use

We or service providers working on our behalf may use the information we collect from and about you for any of the following purposes: (1) to have your gift cards picked up from you or delivered to you; (2) to communicate with you regarding our services and regarding your use of the Plastic Jungle Service; (3) to otherwise fulfill your requests for products and services; (4) to respond to your inquiries; (5) to provide you with targeted content, offers and advertising, such as special offers from merchants whose gift cards you may have in our Online Gift Card Registry or that you have purchased through the Plastic Jungle Service; (6) to contact you when necessary; (7) to ensure that Plastic Jungle Service users are adults and otherwise comply with the Terms; (8) to review Plastic Jungle Service usage and operations and conduct internal marketing and operational research; (9) to address problems with the Plastic Jungle Service, our business or our products and services; (10) to protect the security or integrity of the Plastic Jungle Service and our business, including detecting and addressing fraud and abuse; or (11) to otherwise operate, maintain and provide the features and functionality of the Plastic Jungle Service. We or our service providers may also use the information we have collected from and about you to contact you with promotional materials and offers from us, as well as from our related companies, marketing partners, advertisers and other third parties.

#### Information Disclosure

We care about your privacy, and we will not rent or sell your personal information with third parties for their promotional purposes. We may share the information we collect from and about you with third parties in the following instances:

  * With our service providers, if the disclosure will enable them to fulfill your product or service request or otherwise perform a business, professional or technical support function for us, including, without limitation, the activities described herein, as well as verifying credit card information, fulfilling gift card orders, processing credit card transactions, disbursing payments to Sellers, hosting, developing, and maintaining our service, servers, database, and other systems, enhancing the information that we collect about our customers and transmitting our email. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.
  * On an aggregated or non-personally identifiable basis, to merchants and issuers of gift cards to enable those entities to better understand usage trends with respect to the gift cards they issue, which may include information derived from our Online Gift Card Registry, or to other partners or third parties with respect to aggregated demographic information (such as the ages and zip codes of our Plastic Jungle Service users).
  * As necessary, if we believe that there has been a violation of our Plastic Jungle Terms of Use or of our rights or the rights of any third party;
  * As necessary, to identify, investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities or suspected fraud or other abuse of the Plastic Jungle Service;
  * To respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law; and
  * In the event that Plastic Jungle goes through a business transition, such as a merger, an acquisition by another company, or a sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personal information may be one of the transferred assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

#### Opting Out of Marketing Communications

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at [customersuccess@plasticjungle.com](mailto:customersuccess@plasticjungle.com). 

#### Our Commitment to Data Security

We use certain physical, managerial, and technical safeguards intended to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant against all risks with regards to the security of any information you transmit to us, and so of necessity you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, we again take steps designed to ensure the security of your information on our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If we learn of a security systems breach that affects the privacy of your personal information, then we will attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. We may also post a notice through the Plastic Jungle Service if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach you should notify us at [customersuccess@plasticjungle.com](mailto:customersuccess@plasticjungle.com). 

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [customersuccess@plasticjungle.com](mailto:customersuccess@plasticjungle.com). 

#### Additional Policy Information

##### Blog

Our website offers a publicly accessible blog. You should be aware that any information you provide in this area may be read, collected, and used by others who access such areas. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at customersuccess@plasticjungle.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

##### Customer Testimonials/Comments/Reviews

From time to time, we post customer testimonials/comments/reviews on our website which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at customersuccess@plasticjungle.com. 

#### External Links

The Plastic Jungle Service contains links to third-party websites, which may have privacy policies that differ from ours. Please be aware that Plastic Jungle exercises no control over linked sites and is not responsible for their privacy practices or content. Accordingly, we recommend that you review the privacy policy and terms of use of any website that you access through the Plastic Jungle Service.

#### Social Media Widgets

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button [and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site]. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

#### Children

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, we do not knowingly collect or maintain personal information from persons under 13 years-of-age, and no part of the Plastic Jungle Service is directed to persons under 13. The Plastic Jungle Service is expressly limited to use by persons 18 years of age or above. IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE, THEN PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS THE PLASTIC JUNGLE SERVICE AT ANY TIME OR IN ANY MANNER. If we learn that personal information of persons less than 13-years-of-age has been collected on the Plastic Jungle Service without verifiable parental consent, then we will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. If you are a parent or guardian and discover that your child under the age of 13 has obtained an account on the Plastic Jungle Service, then you may alert us at customersuccess@plasticjungle.com and request that we delete that child's personal information from our systems.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post the changes on the Plastic Jungle Service and update the last updated date of this Privacy Policy. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.

#### Contact Us

If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

Plastic Jungle   
204 East 2nd Avenue, #632  
San Mateo, CA 94401  
Email: [customersuccess@plasticjungle.com](mailto:customersuccess@plasticjungle.com).
